Please.
おねがいします
what are you doing?
何してるの?
What's so?
何がそうなの?
what are you doing?
何してるの?
Come here.
こっち来い
You're the one who talks about Takemochi here.
お前ここのタケモチ言うやつやな
You're going to spread out the photos from before.
お前この前の写真バラ撒くからな
Don't get carried away, come here.
調子乗るな、こっち来い
You're scattering roses.
バラ撒いてるからな、お前
Because I'm definitely spreading roses.
絶対バラ撒いてるからな
Your skin is all over the place, you guys.
お前の肌がバラ撒いてるぞ、お前こら
What should we do?
どうすんね?
What are you sorry for?
何がすみません?
Are you ready?
覚悟できてんの?
Are you OK?
お前はOK?
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいよね?
sorry.
すみません
I'm sorry, you.
す みませんじゃん、お前
What should we do?
どうすんね?
What are you sorry for?
何がすみません?
Because you're spreading out your photos.
お前写真バラ撒いてるからな
The video I shot the other day is also being spread around.
この前撮った動画もバラ撒いてるからな
No, that's impossible.
いや、無理よ
No way, no way.
無理無理
Go home already.
もう帰ってやれ
I'll get ready to scatter the roses.
バラ撒く準備しとくから
Go home.
帰れ
That's the end of the story.
話終わりやね
I have an ID card, so I used my parents' address.
身分証もされてあるし、 実家の住所にしたら、
The rest is fine.
あとはもう、いいよ
I'll do it here.
こっちでやるから
Go home.
帰れよ
please forgive me.
許してください
You don't have a boyfriend, you really have a boyfriend.
お前彼氏おらへんこと、彼氏ほんなんな
Hey.
ねえ
If I were to say it as if it were my boyfriend, I'd say it's annoying.
彼氏のまま言うたら、 ざんまうさやんってな
Na.
な
Sayane is easy to become.
なりやすいのさやね
You're quitting your business.
おままのことやめてるやろ
Na.
な
It's because SLS is spreading it out.
SLSでバラ撒いてるからな
Everyone will know by tomorrow.
明日には全員知ってるやろ
Na.
な
That's good.
よかったやろ
I know everything about your university.
お前の大学の全部知ってるわ
Na.
な
please forgive me.
許してください
I'll do anything.
なんでもします
Will you do anything?
なんでもする?
I can only see it right now.
今すぐにしか見えない
Well then, let's go to the Philippines.
じゃあもうフィリピン行こうか
Na.
な
In the Philippines.
フィリピンでな
Because I have a good job.
いい仕事あるから
Shall we go do that?
それやりに行こうか
Na.
な
It's impossible.
無理です
What, what is impossible?
な、なにが無理やねん
please forgive me.
許してください
Whatever you say.
なんでもそれ言うたらね
So let's go back to the Philippines.
じゃあまたフィリピンにしよっか
Please scatter it and show me the money.
それバラ撒いてお金見せてください
Shall I forgive you?
許しようか
Hey.
ねえ
What should I do?
どうしよう
Just sign the consent form.
同意書だけはサインして
Na.
な
I don't need it.
いらない
Bring the consent form.
同意書持ってこい
Sign the consent form.
同意書サインして
It's impossible.
無理です
That's no good either.
あれもダメ
This is also no good.
これもダメ
Don't go talk.
話しに行かないで
Sign it.
サインして
Is it no good?
ダメでしょうか
Yeah.
うん
Sign it.
サインして
A sign saying I agree.
同意ですっていうサインや
We are you, so we don't mind if we become Filipinos.
俺らはお前さんなんで、 フ ィ リピンになってもいいや
Just write my name.
僕に名前書くだけ
There isn't.
無いよ
Okay.
オッケー
Well then, let's do it.
じゃあやろっか
What did you just do?
今してきたの?
It's here.
やってきたな
Same underwear again.
また同じ下着替え
Change your underwear next.
下着替えを次に
Na.
な
I guess this is just an experience.
このままこれは体験で そうか
Write it on the day after yesterday.
昨日の 次の日に書きましょう
You're throwing your stomach out.
お腹を投げてるな
Is it no good?
ダメでしょうか
Well then, let's take it off.
じゃあ脱いじゃおうか
From above.
上から
Take it off.
脱がせろ
I'll take you outside.
外連れて行くぞ
Come here.
こっち来い
Shall we take a walk around the school?
その学校で散歩しようか
Go this way.
こっち行け
Let's take a walk.
散歩しよう
Take this.
こっち取れ
That's it.
そこだよな
Go here.
こ っち 行け
Let's go home.
ホームに行くぞ
Isn't it good?
良いんじゃないの?
You took this off too.
これも脱がしたろ
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Because I'm wearing pants.
パンツ入ってるから
It won't stop.
止まんから
A beta is coming.
Aベーター来るよ
I'm looking forward to it.
楽しみだね
Yes, ride, ride.
はい、乗って乗って
Shall we go?
行こうか
What should I do?
どうする?
どうするの?
Are you going to me?
お前に行くの?
I don't like it.
嫌です
Well then, bye.
じゃあ、バイバイ
what are you doing?
何してるの?
Go buy me some coffee.
コーヒー買ってこいよ
コーヒー買ってこいって
Come here.
こっち来い
Didn't anyone see it?
誰も見られなかったの?
That's a shame.
残念だな
I didn't expect you to see me.
見られて思わなかったのよな
Go there.
そっち行け
Let's go.
行こうよ
Take me home.
おうちを連れて行け
Come here so you can be seen.
見られてもらって、こっち来い
what are you doing?
何してるの?
You'll find out.
バレちゃうよ
The one who spoke out.
声出したのが
Did you remember?
覚え出したのか?
Want to get everyone's attention?
みんなの注目を集めようか?
Crouch.
しゃがめ
All right, sit down and go.
よいしょ、座っておしとけ
It was seen.
見られちゃったね
I would have liked to see more of it though.
俺は全然、もっと見られてよかったんだけど
Crouch.
しゃがめ
Let's lick it more.
あざくは、もっと舐めすしよう
Shall I sit down and lick it?
座って舐めすしようか
Shall we do an Instagram live?
インスタライブしようか
I'll do an Instagram live.
インスタライブするわ
I'm going to do an Instagram live.
インスタライブしちゃうよ
good?
いい?
Do it.
しちゃって
No good
ダメ
is.
です
What should I do?
どう する?
Back up on the rooftop?
屋上でバックする?
Where will we do it?
どこでやる?
What should I do?
どうすんの?
Don't open that window.
そこの窓開けないで
Should I stand back there?
そこで立ちバックしようか
If you say it out loud, people will find out.
声出したら、バレちゃうよ
Please be careful.
気を付けてください
Do it in a bigger place.
も っと 大きい中でしてやれ
Reina-chan, look here.
レイナちゃん、こっち見て
Let me show it to you again.
ちょっと、もう一回見せてみようか
Come back.
帰ってこい
care
気に
Don't worry, put on a bag.
せ ず、バックを付けてやれ
Go back and do it inside already.
バックで、もう中でしてやれ
I'm going to spread this photo around.
この写真、もうばらまいてやるわ
Say I'm sorry for making you angry.
あけもつしてごめんなさいって言え
Tell your mother, please don't tell her.
お母さんに言わないでくださいって言え
Please don't tell your mother.
お 母さんに言わないでください
Which of your boyfriend's progress do you feel better about?
彼氏の進行が、どっちが気持ちいい?
now.
今
Which one?
どっち?
Does it feel good now?
今のが気持ちいい?
Well then, how about I call you my boyfriend too?
じゃあ、彼氏にも呼ぼうか
Hey, call your boyfriend.
なあ、彼氏に電話しろよ
Let's have a video call.
ビデオ通話しようぜ
Na
な
a?
あ?
Does it feel good?
気 持ちいい?
where?
どこ?
Go, go.
行く、行く
It feels good over there.
あそこ、気持ちいい
It would be hard if my boyfriend saw me.
彼氏に見られたら大変だね
hard?
大変?
I don't like it.
嫌です
Don't like it?
嫌?
I'll cum inside you, come on.
中に出すよ、ほら
Let me out.
出してやれ
Oh my.
あらら
It's coming out inside.
中に出ちゃってるよ、
this.
これ
Come here.
こ っち来い
It's about time.
そろそろやれ
Kupa.
クパしろ
I apologize for the inconvenience this time.
この度は掛け持ちして、申し訳ございません
Say that.
って言え
It feels good.
気持ちいいです
This time,
この度、
Please don't tell your mother.
お 母さんに言わないでください
お母さんに言わないでください
Don't even tell your boyfriend.
彼氏にも言わないでください
to my boyfriend
彼氏に
too.
も
I will bring you 500,000 yen within a week.
1週 間以内に50万円持ってきます
Please don't say it.
言わないでください
言 わないでください
Please don't say it.
言わないでください
Okay.
よ っしゃ
You can go home.
帰っていいよ
I will bring you 500,000 yen within a week.
1週間以内に50万円持ってきます
Got it.
分かった
I'm going home.
帰るわ
Thank you for your hard work.
お疲れ
お疲れさまでした